Sex. Murder. Betrayal. Everything that makes life worth living.
U Turn is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Oliver Stone.
When a desperate man’s car breaks down in a bizarre desert town while evading
vengeful bookies, he becomes entangled in a dangerous love triangle.
Caught between a married couple, he’s faced with
deadly contracts to kill them both.
Bobby Cooper, played by Sean Penn.
Jake McKenna, played by Nick Nolte.
Grace McKenna, played by Jennifer Lopez.
Toby N. Tucker, played by Joaquin Phoenix.
Jenny, played by Claire Danes.
Sheriff Virgil Potter, played by Powers Boothe.
U Turn is a 1997 American neo-noir crime thriller film directed by Oliver Stone, and starring Sean Penn, Billy Bob
Thornton, Jennifer Lopez, Jon Voight, Powers Boothe, Joaquin Phoenix, Claire Danes and Nick Nolte.
It is based on the book Stray Dogs by John
Ridley, who also wrote the screenplay.
U Turn premiered at the Telluride Film Festival on August 27, 1997 before being
released by Sony Pictures Releasing on October 3, 1997 in the United States.
The film grossed $6.6 million in the United States against an estimated $19
million budget, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of small town, robbery,
gambling debt, arizona, wilderness.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.